[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the famous Niagara boat called?", "correct_answer": "Maid of the Mist", "incorrect_answers": ["Niagara-on-the-Lake", "Lady Horseshoe", "Lady of the Mist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary Hollywood actress was the second wife of actor Richard Burton, who passed away in 1984?", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Kelly", "Marilyn Monroe", "Audrey Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Star Wars characters is not part of the Skywalker bloodline?", "correct_answer": "Han Solo", "incorrect_answers": ["Darth Vader", "Princess Leia", "Luke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Use an IMAP server to get advanced mail features.  What does IMAP stand for?", "correct_answer": "Internet Message Access Protocol", "incorrect_answers": ["Intelligent Message Account Process", "Internet Massive Access Peak", "Intelligent Messaging Account Protocol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these psychologists was not a student of Freuds?", "correct_answer": "Ulrich Neisser", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilhelm Reich", "Alfred Adler", "Otto Rank"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many years does a mother grizzly stay with her cubs?", "correct_answer": "1and a half to 3 and a half years", "incorrect_answers": ["5 months to 10 months", "6 weeks to 1 year", "7-8 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People with red hair are more sensitive to thermal pain.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the famous American writer  whose first job was selling and making pencils?", "correct_answer": "Henry David Thoreau", "incorrect_answers": ["John Steinbeck", "Benjamin Franklin", "Nathaniel Hawthorne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual anatomical feature do wombats possess?", "correct_answer": "Their pouch faces backwards.", "incorrect_answers": ["They dont have a spleen.", "They dont have eyelids.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In one of the freecreditreport.com commercials the boys are at the Renaissance Faire. How was the lead singer feeling at the beginning of the song?", "correct_answer": "depressed", "incorrect_answers": ["impressed", "incensed", "regressed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1985 movie, an eccentric scientist fits a time machine into a DeLorean car.", "correct_answer": "Back to the Future", "incorrect_answers": ["Time Waits for Snowman", "Time After Time", "The Time Machine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name \u201cHolland\u201d is equivalent to the name the Netherlands.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]